Now it's time
to go.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Thank you
for
[Music]
asking
business. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
my husband who came here from
Argentina and he saw a young
man like he was back in the day who came
to our country. We have family here but
needed mentorship guidance and
life is not the same for so many people.
[Music]
We
are we
are because
we are standard.
[Music]
to so many organizations throughout
history to his business to
ERC for many many
years to
university foundation.
If you look at
[Music]
LinkedIn and one of the great
Power.
Yes. Yes.
That's
why I watch what this country means
to benefit from this country. It's
interesting what he said. He said
that I learned because of the personal
freedoms in our country. I learn to be
myself. I learned that I can be myself
and I don't have to meet other people's
expectations of myself and that's a
real if you want that gift of our
country is that we are authenticelves I
remember one year when I was in Los
Angeles for our
Chinese if I make a mistake.
So I think it's important for us to
recognize those gifts
that my appreciation to the
end. Thank
you.
Yeah. Heat.
[Music]